William R. Cotter Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Legislative Correspondence, 1971-1981
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - General, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 343)
    - Clean Air Act, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 344)
    - HR 8444 (Energy Bill), 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 345)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 346)
    - Gun Control, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 347)
  - Merchant Marines and Fisheries, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 348)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1977 January - March (Box 23:, Folder 349)
    - 1977 April - June (Box 23:, Folder 350)
    - 1977 July - September (Box 23:, Folder 351)
    - 1977 October - December (Box 24:, Folder 352)
    - Energy Issues, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 353)
    - Northeast: Midwest(Economic Advancement Coalition), 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 354)
  - Poll
    - Thank you, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 355)
    - Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 356)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - General, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 357)
    - HR 10 and 13, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 358)
    - Congressional Pay Raise, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 359)
    - HR 41, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 360)
  - Public Works
    - General, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 361)
    - Airline Deregulation, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 362)
  - Rules, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 362)
  - Science and Technology, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 363)
  - Small Business Administration, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 364)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 365)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 366)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 367)
    - Energy Issues, 1977 January - June (Box 24:, Folder 368)
    - Energy Issues, 1977 July - December (Box 24:, Folder 369)
    - Health, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 370)
    - Health Subcommittee: Hospital Cost Containment, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 371)
    - Public Assistance, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 372)
    - SSA: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 373)
    - SSA, 1977 January 1 - July 17 (Box 25:, Folder 374)
    - SSA, 1977 July 18 - September 30 (Box 25:, Folder 375)
    - SSA, 1977 October - December (Box 25:, Folder 376)
    - Civil Service SSA: Mass Mailing, HR 9346, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 377)
  - Ways and Means
    - SSA: HR 8076, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 378)
    - Taxes, 1977 January - June (Box 25:, Folder 379)
    - Taxes, 1977 July - December (Box 25:, Folder 380)
    - Tax Reform Law, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 381)
    - Taxes: Tax Credit for Tuition Expenses, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 382)
    - RE HR 8818 (To Revise Credit for the Elderly), 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 383)
    - Six Pay Exclusion, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 384)
  - Taxes: Proposal to Reduce 4% Tax on Private Foundations, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 385)
  - Cotter Tax Rebate Amendment: Out of State Correspondence, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 386)
  - Ways and Means
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 387)
    - Trade, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 388)
    - Oversight: Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 389)
    - Welfare Program, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 390)
  - Joint Committees
    - General, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 391)
    - On Internal Revenue Tax, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 392)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Energy: General, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 393)
  - Mobil Oil Ad Correspondence, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 394)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Irish Affairs, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 395)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Outer Continental Shelf, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 396)
  - Select Committees, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 397)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 398)
  - Northeast-Midwest Economic Coalition, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 399)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 400)
  - Agriculture, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 401)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 402)
    - Defense, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 403)
    - Labor: HEW Subcommittee, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 404)
    - HUD: Indent Agency, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 405)
    - Public Works, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 406)
    - Foreign Operations, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 407)
  - Armed Services, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 408)
  - Banking, Currency, & Housing, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 409)
  - Budget, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 410)
  - District of Columbia, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 411)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 412)
    - Labor, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 413)
    - C.E.T.A. Reauthorization, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 414)
    - Education, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 415)
    - HR 50, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 416)
    - HR 6075 (Pregnancy Disability), 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 417)
    - Domestic Violence Act, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 418)
  - Government Operations, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 419)
  - House Administration, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 420)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs
    - General, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 421)
    - Alaska Laps Bill, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 422)
  - Internal Relations
    - Panama Canal, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 423)
    - Resumption of Aid to Turkey, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 424)
    - Middle East Arms Package, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 425)
    - Middle East, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 426)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 427)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - General, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 428)
    - Communications, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 429)
    - Energy, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 430)
    - Health, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 431)
  - Judiciary
    - 1978 January - June (Box 27:, Folder 432)
    - 1978 July - December (Box 27:, Folder 433)
    - Gun Control, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 434)
    - Obscenity, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 435)
    - ERA Extension, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 436)
    - House Resolution 106 (Criminal Code Bill), 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 437)
    - Cigarette Smuggling, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 438)
    - Pro BATF Regulations, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 439)
    - BATF Rustein, Oscar (S. 3128), 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 440)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries
    - General, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 441)
    - Elephant Protection, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 442)
    - Endangered Species, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 443)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1978 January - March (Box 28:, Folder 444)
    - 1978 April - June (Box 28:, Folder 445)
    - 1978 July - September (Box 28:, Folder 446)
    - 1978 October - December (Box 28:, Folder 447)
    - Questionnaires (summer poll), 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 448)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - General, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 449)
    - National Lupus Week, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 450)
    - HR 7700, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 451)
    - Reform HR 11280, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 452)
    - Reform V.A. Pree, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 453)
  - Public Works and Transportation, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 454)
  - Rules, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 455)
  - Science and Technology, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 456)
  - Small Business, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 457)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 458)
  - Ways and Means
    - Special Task Force, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 459)
    - General, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 460)
    - Info Line, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 461)
    - Public Assistance, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 462)
    - SSA: HR 10533, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 463)
    - SSA: Information (international), 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 464)
    - Social Security, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 465)
    - SSA, 1978 June - Present (Box 29:, Folder 466)
    - Taxes (general), 1978 January - June (Box 29:, Folder 467)
    - Taxes (general), 1978 July - December (Box 29:, Folder 468)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 469)
    - Oversight, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 470)
    - Welfare Reform, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 471)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 January - february (Box 29:, Folder 472)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 March (Box 29:, Folder 473)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 April 1 - 15 (Box 29:, Folder 474)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 April 16 - 30 (Box 29:, Folder 475)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 May 1 - 16 (Box 29:, Folder 476)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 June (Box 30:, Folder 477)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 July - August (Box 30:, Folder 478)
    - Tax Reform, 1978 September (Box 30:, Folder 479)
    - Tax Relief for Tuition, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 480)
    - HR 12182 - Pickle Amendment, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 481)
    - $240 Tax Credit, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 482)
    - Trade, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 483)
  - Select Committees, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 484)
  - Joint Committees, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 485)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Energy, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 486)
  - Joint Committee on Taxation, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 487)
  - Ad Hoc Committees: General, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 488)
  - Ad Hoc Committees for Irish Affairs, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 489)
  - Ad Hoc Committees on the Outside Continental Shelf, 1978 (Box 30:, Folder 490)
  - Congressional Textile Caucus, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 491)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 492)
  - Northeast-Midwest Economic Coalition, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 493)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 494)
  - Congressional Port Caucus, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 495)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 496)
    - Food Stamp Act, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 497)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 498)
    - Labor: HEW, Elderly Nutrition, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 499)
    - Defense, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 500)
    - Transportation, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 501)
    - Labor, HEW, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 502)
  - Armed Services, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 503)
  - Banking, Currency, Housing
    - General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 504)
    - Chrysler Bailout, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 505)
  - Budget, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 506)
  - District of Columbia, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 507)
  - Foreign Affairs
    - General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 508)
    - Salt II, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 509)
    - Iran, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 510)
    - Zimbabwe/Rhodesia, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 511)
    - Cambodia, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 512)
    - Middle East, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 513)
    - Panama Canal, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 514)
    - Taiwan, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 515)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 516)
    - Labor, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 517)
    - Asbestos in Schools, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 518)
    - Labor (Davis-Bacon Act), 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 519)
    - Title IX, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 520)
    - Education, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 521)
  - Governmental Operations
    - General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 522)
    - HR 2444 (Education Department), 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 523)
  - Housing Administration, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 524)
  - Interior: General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 525)
  - Interior and Insular: Alaska Lands, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 526)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - General, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 527)
    - Environment, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 528)
    - Health, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 529)
    - Transportation and Commerce, 1979 (Box 31:, Folder 530)
    - Energy, 1979 January - April (Box 31:, Folder 531)
    - Energy, 1979 May - July (Box 32:, Folder 532)
    - Energy, 1979 August - September (Box 32:, Folder 533)
    - Energy, 1979 October - December (Box 32:, Folder 534)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 535)
    - H.J. Res. 395, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 536)
    - Amendment on Busing (J.J. Res. 74), 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 537)
    - Gun Control, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 538)
    - HR 3439 (Amerasians Immigration), 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 539)
    - Abortion, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 540)
    - Abortion, Part II, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 541)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries
    - General, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 542)
    - Congressional Caucus, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 543)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 544)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - General, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 545)
    - H.J. Res. 209, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 546)
    - H.J. Res. 69 “Square Dance”, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 547)
  - HR 4488 (Federal Employee Compensation), Reform Act, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 548)
  - Public Works and Transportation
    - General, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 549)
    - HR 3942 (Aviation Noise), 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 550)
    - Surface Transportation, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 551)
    - Trucking Deregulation, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 552)
  - Rules, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 553)
  - Science and Technology, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 554)
  - Small Business, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 555)
  - Standard of Official Conduct, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 556)
  - Veterans Affairs: General, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 557)
  - Ways and Means
    - Inflation, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 558)
    - General, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 559)
    - Health, 1979 September - December (Box 33:, Folder 560)
    - Tax, 1979 June - September (Box 33:, Folder 561)
    - Tax, 1979 October - December (Box 33:, Folder 562)
    - HR 3712 (Tax Free Housing Bonds), 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 563)
    - Public Assistance, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 564)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 565)
    - Oversight, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 566)
    - Welfare, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 567)
    - SSA, 1979 January - March (Box 33:, Folder 568)
    - SSA, 1979 April - June (Box 33:, Folder 569)
    - SSA, 1979 July - December (Box 33:, Folder 570)
    - SSA: Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 571)
    - SSA: HR 333 and Follow-up, 1979 (Box 33:, Folder 572)
  - Trade
    - HR 1543 (Trade Adjustment Assistance), 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 573)
    - Subcommittee MTN, Wine Gallon Compromise, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 574)
    - U.S. Customs Service and International Trade Comm., 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 575)
    - Subcommittee MTN, Aircraft Agreement, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 576)
    - Subcommittee MTN, Wine Gallon Compromise correspondence, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 577)
    - Distilled Spirits, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 578)
    - Sugar, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 579)
    - Russian Watches, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 580)
  - Joint Committees, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 581)
  - Select Committees, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 582)
  - Ad Hoc Committees, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 583)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 584)
  - Northeast-Midwest Economic Advancement Coalition, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 585)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 586)
  - Agriculture
    - Food Stamps, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 587)
    - General, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 588)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 589)
    - Labor: HEW, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 590)
    - LEAA, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 591)
    - HUD: Indian Agreement, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 592)
    - Defense, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 593)
  - Supplemental and Recession, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 594)
  - Armed Services
    - Draft Registration, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 595)
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 596)
  - Banking, Currency, and Housing, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 597)
  - Budget
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 598)
    - Defense, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 599)
  - District of Columbia, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 600)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 601)
    - Education, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 602)
  - Foreign Affairs
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 603)
    - Middle East, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 604)
    - SALT II, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 605)
    - Special Central American Assistant: HR 6081 (Aid to Nicaragua), 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 606)
      - Iran, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 607)
  - Education and Labor: Labor, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 608)
  - Government Operations, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 609)
  - House Administration, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 610)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 611)
    - HR 5981 (Barrier Islands), 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 612)
  - Interior: Nuclear Energy, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 613)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 614)
    - Health, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 615)
    - Energy, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 616)
    - Steel-Jawed Traps, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 617)
  - Housing and Community Development, 1980 (Box 35A, Box 35:, Folder 618)
  - Judiciary
    - Cults, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 619)
    - Abortion Pro-choice, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 620)
    - Anti-abortion, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 621)
    - General, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 622)
    - Judge Dollings Decisions, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 623)
    - Balanced Budgets, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 624)
    - Gun Control, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 625)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 626)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1980 January - June (Box 35:, Folder 627)
    - 1980 July - December (Box 35:, Folder 628)
    - Newsletter: Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 629)
    - Questionnaires, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 630)
    - Questionnaires, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 631)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - General, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 632)
    - COLA, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 633)
  - Public Works and Transportation
    - General, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 634)
    - Surface Transportation, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 635)
    - Aviation Subcommittee, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 636)
    - Trucking Deregulation, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 637)
  - Rules, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 638)
  - Science and Technology, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 639)
  - Small Business Administration, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 640)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 641)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 642)
  - Ways and Means
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 643)
    - Trade Suspension of Duty on RR Freight Cars, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 644)
    - Inflation, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 645)
    - General, 1980 July - December (Box 36:, Folder 646)
    - General, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 647)
    - General: IRS Pension Regs Proposal, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 648)
    - Health, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 649)
    - SSA, 1980 January - May (Box 36:, Folder 650)
    - SSA, 1980 June - December (Box 36:, Folder 651)
    - Taxes, 1980 April 15 - July 31 (Box 36:, Folder 652)
    - Taxes, 1980 august - December (Box 37:, Folder 653)
    - Taxes: Witholding/Interest/Dividends, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 654)
    - Taxes: Windfall Profits, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 655)
    - HR 3904: Multi-Employer Pension Plan, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 656)
    - Taxes: Pensions, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 657)
  - Independent Contractors, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 658)
  - Joint Committees, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 659)
  - Select Committees, 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 660)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 661)
  - Northeast-Midwest Coalition, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 662)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 663)
  - Agriculture
    - Food Stamps, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 664)
    - Child Nutrition Programs, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 665)
    - General, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 666)
  - Appropriations
    - HUD, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 667)
    - H.H.S., 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 668)
    - General, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 669)
    - Electric Boat, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 670)
  - Armed Services, 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 671)
  - Banking, Currency, and Housing
    - MMF, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 672)
    - Currency and Housing, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 673)
  - Budget
    - Defense, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 674)
    - Support Economic Recovery, 1981 January - May (Box 38:, Folder 675)
  - Education and Labor
    - Education, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 676)
    - General, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 677)
    - Education (Title I, E.S.E.A.), 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 678)
    - Education (Vocational), 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 679)
    - Labor, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 680)
    - Education (Arts & Humanities), 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 681)
  - Energy and Commerce
    - Transportation, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 682)
    - Energy, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 683)
    - Environment, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 684)
    - Health, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 685)
  - Foreign Affairs
    - General, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 686)
    - AWACS/F15s Saudi Arabia, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 687)
    - Saudi Arabia: Sales, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 688)
    - Iran, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 689)
  - Government Operations, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 690)
  - House Administration, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 691)
  - Interior
    - Nuclear Power, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 692)
    - General, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 693)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 694)
    - Balanced Budget, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 695)
    - Immigration, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 696)
    - S 481 (School Prayer), 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 697)
    - S 613 (Hobbs Act), 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 698)
    - Legal Services Corporation, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 699)
    - Cults, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 700)
    - Gun Control, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 701)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 702)
  - Miscellaneous
    - General, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 703)
    - General, 1981 January - April (Box 39:, Folder 704)
    - Newsletter Responses, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 705)
    - Questionnaire Responses, 1981 (Box 39:, Folder 706)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 707)
  - Public Works and Transportation
    - General, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 708)
    - Transportation, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 709)
  - Rules, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 710)
  - Science and Technology, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 711)
  - Small Business Administration, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 712)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 713)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 714)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 715)
    - SSA, 1981 January - March (Box 40:, Folder 716)
    - SSA, 1981 April - May (Box 40:, Folder 717)
    - SSA, 1981 May - June (Box 40:, Folder 718)
    - SSA, 1981 July - September (Box 40:, Folder 719)
    - SSA: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 720)
    - SSA: Hartford, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 721)
    - SSA: Health, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 722)
    - SSA: Minimum Payment Plan, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 723)
    - Taxes: Tuition Tax Credit, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 724)
    - Taxes: Cotter Plan, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 725)
    - Taxes: Select Revenue Measures, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 726)
    - Taxes: General, 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 727)
    - Tax Act, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 728-729)
    - Taxes: Fringe Benefits, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 730-731)
    - Taxes: Fringe Benefits (Airline Tickets), 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 732)
    - Support/Oppose Reagan Tax Bill, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 733)
    - HR 2250: Excise Tax on Fish, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 734)
  - Ways and Means
    - Trade, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 735)
    - Public Assistance, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 736)
    - Oversight, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 737)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 738)
    - Welfare, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 739)
    - Joint Committees, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 740)
    - Select Committees, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 741)
- Series II: Executive Records, 1971-1981
  - Agriculture, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 742)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 743)
  - Civil Rights Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 744)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 744)
  - Commerce, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 745)
  - Cost of Living Council, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 746)
  - Defense
    - General, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 747)
    - Calley Trials, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 748)
    - Army, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 749)
    - Navy, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 750)
    - Anti-Pollution Standards: Coast Guard & EPA, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 751)
    - Environment-General, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 752)
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 753)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 754)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 755)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 756)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 757)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 758)
  - Federal Maritime Commission, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 759)
  - General Services Administration, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 760)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 761)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD)
    - General, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 762)
    - Brooke Amendment Application, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 763)
  - Department of the Interior
    - General, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 764)
    - Bushnell Park/I-84, 1971 (Box 42:, Folder 765)